wittysparks.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy - WittySparks

Skip to content

## WittySparks.com: PRIVACY POLICY

WittySparks, which owns and manage the website www.WittySparks.com appreciates your support and knows you care about the privacy of your personal information, and we treat it very seriously. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes what information we collect and how it is used and disclosed in our website. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact the team at admin@wittysparks.com

This Policy is only for the information we gather during your use of WittySparks.com, which has many links to other Web sites. Those other external sites will have their own privacy policy regarding the collection and use of personal information or data. We encourage you to learn about these other sites’ privacy and security policies before providing them with your personal information.

 **WittySparks Comments Policy:**  
Any information you personally submit on our comments page becomes public available information. WittySparks.com is more of public oriented site, as on most of the things we may not control the users information and advise you to use your discretion while sharing your information on the internet. All the information you share or submit is optional, we never force you to submit your personal data online. So we encourage you to to take care of yourself while you disclose your personal information online with others.

 **Information Sharing:**  
We do not sell or rent your personal information collected via comments or forums or Blogs or Videos. Only you have access to your own commenting system account or accounts in forums or blogs or videos which are protected by your own passwords.

 **WittySparks Blogs, Videos, Forums Policy:**  
Individual User or Person is completely responsible for the content or information shared to public via Forums, Blogs or Videos and the user details are mention on each post to identify the person who share the information. So they take the rights of their own content.

 **Give Credit to WittySparks if you use our information:**  
We don’t give permission to use complete data in any other website even after giving credit to WittySparks. But you are always welcome to use short clip of text from WittySparks in your website or blogs or forums as long as you provide credit to WittySparks via a link to the page from where you pick the content.

 **Changes to the privacy policy:**  
This Privacy Policy may be revised or modified or updated any time. So we request you to check and ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version of Privacy Policy. If we updated the policy we will change the “Modified Date” at the bottom of this page.

 _Modified Date: September 26, 2011_
